Guide to the R. Philip Hanes Papers, 1928-2010 RL.00503
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Geographic Series, 1928-1983, undated
  - North Carolina, Winston-Salem: Bell Telephone Hour, 1966 (Box 29)
  - North Carolina, Winston-Salem: Bicentennial, 1966 (Box 29)
  - North Carolina, Winston-Salem: Chamber of Commerce, 1966-1967 (Box 29)
  - North Carolina, Winston-Salem: Correspondence, 1959-1969 (Box 29)
  - North Carolina, Winston-Salem: Craft Shop, 1967 (Box 29)
  - North Carolina, Winston-Salem: Ehle, John, 1963-1970 (Box 29)
  - North Carolina, Winston-Salem: Gallery of Contemporary Art, 1956-1968 (Box 29)
  - North Carolina, Winston-Salem: Gallery of Contemporary Art--Correspondence, 1958-1969 (Box 29)
  - North Carolina, Winston-Salem: Gallery of Contemporary Art--Georgia Section, 1967-1968 (Box 29)
  - North Carolina, Winston-Salem: Governor's School, 1962-1967 (Box 29)
  - North Carolina, Winston-Salem: Hanes Community Center, 1958-1959 (Box 29)
  - North Carolina, Winston-Salem: Hanes Dye and Finishing, 1967-1969 (Box 29)
  - North Carolina, Winston-Salem: Junior League Follies, 1961 (Box 29)
  - North Carolina, Winston-Salem: Little Theater, 1959-1966 (Box 30)
  - North Carolina, Winston-Salem: Model Cities Experiment in Self-Reliance, 1968-1969 (Box 30)
  - North Carolina, Winston-Salem: Moravian Music Fund, Festival, 1957-1968 (Box 30)
  - North Carolina, Winston-Salem: Nature Science Museum, 1964-1968 (Box 30)
  - North Carolina, Winston-Salem: Neighborhood Youth Board, 1969 (Box 30)
  - North Carolina, Winston-Salem: North Carolina School of the Arts--Annual Report, 1965-1966 (Box 30)
  - North Caorlina, Winston-Salem: North Carolina School of the Arts--Brochures, 1966-1967 and undated (Box 30)
  - North Carolina, Winston-Salem: North Carolina School of the Arts--Clippings, 1964-1970 (Box 30)
  - North Carolina, Winston-Salem: North Carolina School of the Arts--Correspondence, 1961-1966, 2 folders (Box 30)
  - North Carolina, Winston-Salem: North Carolina School of the Arts--Correspondence, Jan. l967-1970, and and undated, 3 folders (Box 31)
  - North Carolina, Winston-Salem: North Carolina School of the Arts--Foundation (Box 31)
  - North Carolina, Winston-Salem: North Carolina School of the Arts--Fund Raising, 1965-1966 (Box 31)
  - North Carolina, Winston-Salem: North Carolina School of the Arts--Minutes of Board of Trustee, 1964-1969 (Box 31)
  - North Carolina, Winston-Salem: North Carolina School of the Arts--Miscellaneous, 1961-1967 (Box 31)
  - North Carolina, Winston-Salem: North Carolina School of the Arts--Miscellaneous, 1967-1970 and undated (Box 32)
  - North Carolina, Winston-Salem: North Carolina School of the Arts--Newsletter, 1966-1969 (Box 32)
  - North Carolina, Winston-Salem: North Carolina School of the Arts--News Releases, 1962-1970 (Box 32)
  - North Carolina, Winston-Salem: North Carolina School of the Arts--North Carolina Essay, 1968-1969, Feb-May, 1969-1970, May, 3 folders (Box 32)
  - North Carolina, Winston-Salem: Old Salem, 1961-1968 (Box 32)
  - North Carolina, Winston-Salem: Old Salem, undated (Box 33)
  - North Carolina, Winston-Salem: Piedmont Chamber Orchestra, 1968 (Box 33)
  - North Carolina, Winston-Salem: Piedmont Craftsman Association, 1966 (Box 33)
  - North Carolina, Winston-Salem: Piedmont University Center, 1962-1965 (Box 33)
  - North Carolina, Winston-Salem: Reynolda House, 1968 (Box 33)
  - North Carolina, Winston-Salem: Salem College, 1967-1969 (Box 33)
  - North Carolina, Winston-Salem: Tanglewood, 1962-1964 (Box 33)
  - North Carolina, Winston-Salem: Wake Forest Univ., 1960-1970 (Box 33)
  - North Carolina, Winston-Salem: Salem Foundation, 1961-1969 (Box 33)
  - North Carolina, Winston-Salem: Winston Salem Symphony, 1957-1963 (Box 33)
  - North Carolina: Winston-Salem Symphony, 1964-1968 and undated (Box 33)
  - North Carolina, Winston-Salem: Winston Salem Symphony--Clippings and Correspondence, 1951-1968 (Box 33)
  - North Dakota, 1967 (Box 33)
  - Ohio: Arts Council, 1968 (Box 33)
  - Ohio: Festival, Surveys, 1961-1969 (Box 33)
  - Ohio: Historical Societies, 1960-1962 (Box 33)
  - Ohio: University Schools, 1956-1966 (Box 33)
  - Ohio, Akron, 1960-1962 (Box 33)
  - Ohio, Cincinnati, 1958-1966 (Box 33)
  - Ohio, Cleveland, 1961-1968 (Box 34)
  - Ohio, Columbus, 1961-1967 (Box 34)
  - Ohio, Dayton, 1951-1962 (Box 34)
  - Ohio, Mansfield, 1961-1963 (Box 34)
  - Oklahoma: Arts Council, 1961-1967 (Box 34)
  - Oklahoma, Oklahoma City, 1961-1967 (Box 34)
  - Ohio, Tulsa, 1960-1968 and undated (Box 34)
  - Oklahoma, Tulsa, 1964-1968 and undated (Box 34)
  - Oregon, 1961-1967, 2 folders (Box 34)
  - Pennsylvania, 1961-1967, 2 folders (Box 34)
  - Pennsylvania, Erie, 1961-1963 (Box 35)
  - Pennsylvania, Philadelphia, 1960-1969 and undated (Box 35)
  - Pennsylvania, Philadelphia: Academy--Fine Arts, Museum of Art, 1962-1968 (Box 35)
  - Pennsylvania, Philadelphia: Federal Reserve Bank, 1962 (Box 35)
  - Pennsylvania, Philadelphia: Opera, Orchestra, Settlement Music, 1961-1968 (Box 35)
  - Pennsylvania, Pittsburgh, 1961-1964 (Box 35)
  - Pennsylvania, Tamiment, 1955-1961 (Box 35)
  - Puerto Rico, 1963-1967 (Box 35)
  - Rhode Island, 1961-1967 (Box 35)
  - South Carolina, 1960-1969 (Box 35)
  - South Carolina, Charleston, 1957-1962 (Box 35)
  - South Carolina, Greenville, 1960-1965 (Box 35)
  - South Carolina, Spartanburg, 1959-1969 (Box 35)
  - Tennessee, 1957-1968 (Box 35)
  - Tennessee: Alliance for Progress, 1965 (Box 35)
  - Tennessee: Southeastern Regional Arts Council, 1966 (Box 35)
  - Tennessee, Bristol, 1961-1969 (Box 36)
  - Tennessee, Bristol: Vaten School of Crafts-Project, 1967, Sept. (Box 36)
  - Tennessee, Chattanooga, 1958-1966 (Box 36)
  - Tennessee, Knoxville, 1961-1966 (Box 36)
  - Tennessee, Nashville, 1961-1963 (Box 36)
  - Tennessee, Nashville: Metropolitan Nashville Arts Commission, 1978-1983 and undated (Box 36)
  - Texas, 1960-1966 (Box 36)
  - Texas, Austin, 1961-1962 (Box 36)
  - Texas, Dallas, 1959-1967 (Box 36)
  - Texas, Fort Worth, 1960-1968 (Box 36)
  - Texas, Houston, 1962-1966 (Box 36)
  - Texas, San Antonio, 1961-1966 (Box 36)
  - Utah, 1961-1966 (Box 37)
  - Utah: Symphony, 1961-1963, 2 folders (Box 37)
  - Vermont, 1960-1968 (Box 37)
  - Virginia, 1960-1967 and undated (Box 37)
  - Virginia: Federated Arts of Virginia, 1950-1965 (Box 37)
  - Virginia: Old Dominion Foundation, 1959-1967 (Box 37)
  - Virginia, Abington: Barter Theatre, 1965-1968 (Box 37)
  - Virginia, Charlottesville: Virginia Center for the Creative Arts, 1971-1973 (Box 37)
  - Virginia, Fairfax County, 1965-1968 (Box 37)
  - Virginia, Lynchburg: Fine Arts Center, 1960-1966 (Box 38)
  - Virginia, Norfolk: Tidewater Arts Council, 1959-1965 (Box 38)
  - Virginia, Reston, 1967 (Box 38)
  - Virginia, Richmond, 1960-1967 (Box 38)
  - Virginia, Richmond: Museum of the Arts, 1958-1968 (Box 38)
  - Virginia, Roanoke: Fine Arts Center, Symphony, 1959-1965 (Box 38)
  - Virginia, Williamsburg, 1963 (Box 38)
  - Washington, DC, 1960-1969 (Box 38)
  - Washington, DC: Arts Council, 1965-1968 (Box 38)
  - Washington, DC: Corcoran Gallery, 1961-1966 (Box 38)
  - Washington, DC: Dance, 1965-1966 (Box 38)
  - Washington, DC: Ford's Theater, 1968 (Box 38)
  - Washington, DC: John F. Kennedy Center for the Performing Arts, 1958-1963, Mar., 2 folders (Box 38)
  - Washington, DC: John F. Kennedy Center for the Performing Arts, 1963, June-1964, Dec. and undated, 2 folders (Box 39)
  - Washington, DC: John F. Kennedy Center for the Performing Arts--Clippings, 1962-1964 (Box 39)
  - Washington, DC: John F. Kennedy Center for the Performing Arts--Correspondence, 1960-1969 (Box 39)
  - Washington, DC: Music, 1961-1966 (Box 39)
  - Washington, DC: National Symphony Orchestra, 1958-1964 (Box 39)
  - Washington, DC: Smithsonian Institution, 1963-1969 and undated (Box 39)
  - Washington, DC: Surveys, Art Galleries, Museums, 1961-1970 (Box 39)
  - Washington, DC: Theater and Ballet, 1961-1963 (Box 39)
  - Washington, DC: Trip of the First Lady, 1968 (Nov.) (Box 39)
  - Washington, DC: White House, 1961-1965 (Box 39)
  - Washington, DC: White House Festival of the Arts, 1964-1965 (Box 39)
  - Washington, DC: Workshops for Careers in the Arts, 1968-1970 (Box 40)
  - Washington, DC, 1961-1968 and undated (Box 40)
  - West Virginia, 1961-1969 (Box 40)
  - West Virginia, Charleston: Charleston Art Gallery, 1960-1968 (Box 40)
  - Wisconsin, 1961-1970 (Box 40)
  - Wisconsin: State Arts Council, 1962-1967 (Box 40)
  - Wisconsin: University of Wisconsin, 1962-1967 and undated, 2 folders (Box 40)
  - Wisconsin, LaCrosse, 1967 (Box 40)
  - Wisconsin, Milwaukee: Arts Council, 1961-1968 (Box 40)
  - Wisconsin, Osh Kosh: Civil Symphony, 1961-1965 (Box 41)
  - Wisconsin, Racine: Wingspread Johnson Foundation, 1961-1963 (Box 41)
  - Wyoming (Box 41)
  - Foreign, 1962-1966 (Box 41)
  - Argentina, 1965 (Box 41)
  - Australia, 1962-1967 (Box 41)
  - Austria, 1963 (Box 41)
  - Belgium, 1963 (Box 41)
  - Canada, 1960-1968 and undated (Box 41)
  - Canada: Canada Council, 1962-1963 and undated (Box 41)
  - Canada, Alberta, Calgary, 1960-1963 (Box 41)
  - Canada, British Columbia, Vandouver, 1957-1963 (Box 41)
  - Canada, Manitoba, Winnipeg, 1961-1964 and undated (Box 41)
  - Canada, Ontario: Arts Council, 1963-1966 and undated (Box 41)
  - Canada, Ontario, Ottawa, 1963-1965 (Box 41)
  - Canada, Ontario: Stratford Festival, 1962-1965 (Box 41)
  - Canada, Ontario and Toronto, 1961-1966 (Box 41)
  - Canada, Ontario, Windsor, 1961-1962 (Box 41)
  - Canada, Quebec and Montreal, 1964-1965 and undated (Box 42)
  - Canada, Saskatchewan, 1965 (Box 42)
  - Canada: Universities, 1962-1967 (Box 42)
  - Denmark, 1961 and 1968 (Box 42)
  - France, 1961 (Box 42)
  - Germany, 1968 (Box 42)
  - Great Britain, 1958-1969 and undated (Box 42)
  - Great Britain: Arts Council, 1945-1970 (Box 42)
  - Great Britain: Music Theatre, 1960-1965 (Box 42)
  - Greece, 1961 (Box 42)
  - Guatemala, 1965 (Box 42)
  - Indonesia, 1964 (Box 42)
  - Italy, 1961-1967 (Box 42)
  - Japan, undated (Box 42)
  - Netherlands, 1961-1967 (Box 42)
  - Peru, 1964-1967 (Box 42)
  - Soviet Union, 1961-1964 (Box 42)
  - Switzerland, 1963 (Box 42)
  - Thailand, 1963 (Box 42)
  - West Indies, 1968 (Box 42)
- Subject Files Series, 1945?1973 and undated
  Files of arts organizations, but also includes some general topics, such as architects, art education, art and economics, finance and the arts, and publicity. About one-fourth of the series is correspondence and memoranda, but also includes mimeographed and printed material. There are newsletters, reports and financial reports, minutes and agendas of meetings, press releases, clippings, and a few speeches. Arranged alphabetically by name of arts organization or topic.
  - Actors' Equity Association, 1962-1966 (Box 43)
  - Amateur Chamber Music Players, 1956-1961 (Box 43)
  - American Academy of Arts and Letters, 1966 (Box 43)
  - American Association of Museums, 1959-1969 (Box 43)
  - American Ballet Theater, 1968 (Box 43)
  - American Community Theater, n.d (Box 43)
  - American Composers Alliance, 1961-1963 (Box 43)
  - American Craftsmen's Council, 1965-1971 (Box 43)
  - American Educational Theatre Association, 1960-1965 (Box 43)
  - AFL-CIO: Community Services, 1961-1963 and undated (Box 43)
  - American Recreation Society, 1961 (Box 43)
  - American Society of Composers, Authors, and Publishers, undated (Box 43)
  - American Federation of Arts, 1959 (Box 43)
  - American Federation of Musicians, 1964-1966 (Box 43)
  - American Film Institute, 1967-1970 (Box 43)
  - American Guild of Musical Artists, 1958-1966 (Box 43)
  - American Illustrative Art Musem, 1968 (Box 43)
  - AIA Journal, 1967 (Box 43)
  - American Institute of Management, undated (Box 43)
  - American Musical Digest, 1969 (Box 43)
  - American National Theatre and Academy, 1952-1965 (Box 43)
  - American Symphony Orchestra League: General, 1956-1970 and undated (Box 44)
  - American Symphony Orchestra League: Arts Councils, 1956-1959 (Box 44)
  - American Symphony Orchestra League: Convention Meetings, 1956-1962 (Box 44)
  - American Symphony Orchestra League: Conventions, Meetings, 1961-1968 (Box 44)
  - American Symphony Orchestra League: Convention Programs, 1955-1969 (Box 44)
  - American Symphony Orchestra League: Correspondence, 1957-1970 (Box 45)
  - American Symphony Orchestra League: Federal Legislation, 1961-1968 (Box 45)
  - American Symphony Orchestra League: Finances, 1960-1965 (Box 45)
  - American Symphony Orchestra League: Institutes and Workshops, 1960-1966 (Box 45)
  - American Symphony Orchestra League: Memos, Miscellaneous, 1957-1967 (Box 45)
  - American Symphony Orchestra League: Reports, 1957-1968 (Box 45)
  - American Symphony Orchestra League: Surveys, 1957-1963 (Box 45)
  - American Symphony Orchestra League: Women's Council, 1960-1965 (Box 46)
  - Appalachian Regional Commission, 1966 (Box 46)
  - Applications for Positions, 1965-1966 (Box 46)
  - Architects, 1965 (Box 46)
  - Archives of American Art, 1964 (Box 46)
  - Arey, June, 1965-1966 (Box 46)
  - Art and Economics, 1966 (Box 46)
  - Art and Sports, 1963-1965 (Box 46)
  - Art Education, 1966 (Box 46)
  - Arts Administration Institute, 1963-1966 (Box 46)
  - Arts Councils, 1956-1971 and undated (Box 46)
  - Arts Management, 1957-1969 and undated (Box 47)
  - Arts Management, Questionnaires, 1962 and ca. 1962 (Box 48)
  - Arts Management: Reiss, Alvin H. 1955-1969 (Box 48)
  - Associated Councils of the Arts, 1960-1967 (Box 49)
  - Associated Councils of the Arts, 1966-1972 and undated (Box 50)
  - Associated Councils of the Arts: Assembly of State and Provincial Arts, 1968-1969 (Box 50)
  - Associated Councils of the Arts: Award, 1963-1966 (Box 50)
  - Associated Councils of the Arts: Board of Directors, 1960-1967 (Box 50)
  - Associated Councils of the Arts: Board of Directors, 1967-1969 and undated (Box 51)
  - Associated Councils of the Arts: Board of Directors--Agenda, 1965-1968 (Box 51)
  - Associated Councils of the Arts: Board of Directors--Brochures, 1965 (Box 51)
  - Associated Councils of the Arts: Board of Directors--Buffet, 1969 (Box 51)
  - Associated Councils of the Arts: Board of Directors--Correspondence, 1963-1968 (Box 51)
  - Associated Councils of the Arts: Board of Directors--Director's Manual, 1964 (Box 51)
  - Associated Councils of the Arts: Board of Directors--Executive Committee, 1962-1968 (Box 51)
  - Associated Councils of the Arts: Board of Directors--Meeting, 1966 (Box 51)
  - Associated Councils of the Arts: Board of Directors--Meetings, 1967-1969 (Box 52)
  - Associated Councils of the Arts: Board of Directors--Memos, 1963-1968 (Box 52)
  - Associated Councils of the Arts: Board of Directors, 1963-1966 (Box 53)
  - Associated Councils of the Arts: Budgets and Financial Reports, 1963-1969 (Box 53)
  - Associated Councils of the Arts: Bulletins, 1960-1966 (Box 53)
  - Associated Councils of the Arts: Business Council, 1967 (Box 53)
  - Associated Councils of the Arts: By-Laws, Organization, etc., 1959-1967 (Box 53)
  - Associated Councils of the Arts: Center for Studies in the Arts, 1967 (Box 53)
  - Associated Councils of the Arts: Conferences (Pre-1965), 1960-1965 (Box 53)
  - Associated Council of the Arts: Conferences (1965), 1965 (Box 53)
  - Associated Councils of the Arts: Conference (1965), 1966 and undated (Box 54)
  - Associated Councils of the Arts: Conference (1965), 1965 (Box 54)
  - Associated Councils of the Arts: Conference (1965)--Photographs, 1965 (Box 54)
  - Associated Councils of the Arts: Conference (1965, NYC), 1965-1966 (Box 54)
  - Associated Councils of the Arts: Conference (1966), 1965-1966 and undated (Box 54)
  - Associated Councils of the Arts: Conference (1967), 1965-1967 (Box 54)
  - Associated Councils of the Arts: Conference (1968), 1968 and undated (Box 54)
  - Associated Councils of the Arts: Cultural Affairs, 1967-1968 (Box 54)
  - Associated Councils of the Arts: Endowment Funds, 1965 (Box 54)
  - Associated Councils of the Arts: Endowment Fund--Contribution, 1965-1968 (Box 55)
  - Associated Councils of the Arts: Executive Committee, 1968 (Box 55)
  - Associated Councils of the Arts: Films, 1967 (Box 55)
  - Associated Councils of the Arts: Fund Raising--Avalon, Babcock, Burgard, Carnegie, Danforth, Ford, General, Knox, NYT, Old Dominion, US Steel, 1965 (Box 55)
  - Associated Councils of the Arts: Handbook #1, 1961-1966 (Box 55)
  - Associated Councils of the Arts: Handbook #2, 1963-1965 and undated (Box 55)
  - Associated Councils of the Arts: Hanes, Philip,--Correspondence, 1959-1966 (Box 55)
  - Associated Councils of the Arts: Hanes, Philip--Correspondence, 1966-1969 and undated (Box 56)
  - Associated Councils of the Arts: Irwin, George M.--Correspondence, 1962-1966 (Box 56)
  - Associated Councils of the Arts: Library, 1965-1967 (Box 56)
  - Associated Councils of the Arts: Materials for Library Distribution, 1961-1967 and undated (Box 56)
  - Associated Councils of the Arts: Memberships, 1963-1968 and undated (Box 56)
  - Associated Councils of the Arts: Memos, 1962-1969 (Box 57)
  - Associated Councils of the Arts: Name Change, 1964-1966 (Box 57)
  - Associated Councils of the Arts: National Endowment Proposal, 1967 (Box 57)
  - Associated Councils of the Arts: National Office, 1961-1968 and undated (Box 57)
  - Associated Councils of the Arts: Newsline, 1964-1966 (Box 57)
  - Associated Councils of the Arts: Notebook 1, undated (Box 57)
  - Associated Councils of the Arts: Notebook 2, undated (Box 58)
  - Associated Councils of the Arts: Projects, 1966-1970 (Box 58)
  - Associated Councils of the Arts: Projects, 1970-1973 and undated (Box 59)
  - Associated Councils of the Arts: Projects, 1971-1973 and undated (Box 60)
  - Associated Councils of the Arts: Prospectus, 1966-1968 (Box 60)
  - Associated Councils of the Arts: Report, 1969 (Box 60)
  - Arts Council of America: Requests, Establishment of Brochures, etc., 1963-1967 (Box 60)
  - Associated Councils of the Arts: State Arts Council Guide, 1966 (Box 60)
  - Associated Councils of America: State Arts Councils General, 1964-1968 (Box 60)
  - Associated Councils of the Arts: Studies and Projects, 1967-1969 (Box 60)
  - Authors League of America, 1959 (Box 60)
  - Benjamin, Edward B., 1959-1965 (Box 61)
  - Bibliographies, 1963-1965 (Box 61)
  - "Black Panther Coloring Book," undated (Box 61)
  - Bravo, 1965-1966 (Box 61)
  - The Business Committee for the Arts, 1966-1969 (Box 61)
  - Business Support of the Arts, 1963-1967 (Box 61)
  - Christmas Cards, 1965-1966 (Box 61)
  - Committee to Rescue Italian Art, 1966-1967 (Box 61)
  - Conservation, 1970 (Box 61)
  - Construction and Design, 1953-1966 and undated, 2 folders (Box 61)
  - Council and Leaders and Specialists, 1965 (Box 62)
  - Crafts, 1965-1970 (Box 62)
  - Creativity, 1964 (Box 62)
  - Culture, 1960-1970 (Box 62)
  - Dance, 1962-1969 (Box 62)
  - Dance Notation Bureau, 1969 (Box 62)
  - De Mille (Prude), Agnes, 1966-1970 (See N.C. Winston-Salem NCSA Correspondence) (Box 62)
  - Duberman, Martin, 1967-1968 (Box 62)
  - Education, 1960-1965 (Box 62)
  - Engle, Paul, 1969 (Box 62)
  - Equipment, 1963 (Box 62)
  - Esquire: BCA-Art Awards, 1965-1970 (Box 62)
  - Esquire: BCA-Art Awards, Entries, 1968-1969 Feb. 14-1969 Feb. 15-March, 2 folders (Box 63)
  - Festivals, 1963-1964 (Box 63)
  - Finance and the Arts, 1959-1966 (Box 63)
  - Federation of Communities in Service, 1967-1968 (Box 63)
  - Foundations, 1964-1967 (Box 63)
  - Foundations: Carnegie, 1966 (Box 63)
  - Foundations: Community, 1962 (Box 63)
  - Foundations: Ford, 1960-1968 (Box 63)
  - Foundations: Glide, 1968 (Box 63)
  - Foundations: Johnson, 1961-1964 (Box 63)
  - Foundations: Quincy, 1968 (Box 63)
  - Foundations: Rockefeller, 1963-1966, Sept. (Box 63)
  - Foundations: Rockefeller, 1966, Oct.-1969 and undated (Box 64)
  - Foundations: Russell Sage, 1964-1965 (Box 64)
  - Foundations: Twentieth Century Fund, 1964-1967 (Box 64)
  - Foundations: U.S. Steel, 1962 (Box 64)
  - The Fund Raising Institute, undated (Box 64)
  - Fundraising, 1962-1969 (Box 64)
  - Fundraising and Development, 1958-1964 (Box 64)
  - Fundraising: National Conference on Solicitations, 1954-1955 (Box 64)
  - Girl Scouts: World of Arts Conference, 1969 (Box 64)
  - Government and the Arts, 1961-1969 (Box 64)
  - Graphic Arts, 1961-1965 (Box 64)
  - Guggenheim, Peggy, 1969 (Box 64)
  - Hanes, R. P., Jr., 1962-1970 (Box 64)
  - Hanes, R. P., Jr.: Personal, 1960-1968 Aug. 1968 Sep.-1969 and undated, 2 folders (Box 65)
  - Hanes, R. P., Jr.: Speeches and Material, 1961-1966 (Box 65)
  - Haryou Act, 1965 (Box 65)
  - Howe, Harold, 1967 (Box 65)
  - International Platform Association, undated (Box 65)
  - Junior League, 1962-1967 (Box 65)
  - Legislation, 1966 (Box 65)
  - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts, 1958-1965 (Box 65)
  - Managers: College and University Concerts, 1961 (Box 65)
  - Morris, Joe Alex, 1959-1960 (Box 65)
  - Motion Pictures, 1962 (Box 65)
  - Museum Management, 1962-1967 (Box 65)
  - Music, 1959-1966 and undated, 2 folders (Box 65)
  - National Arts and Humanities Foundation, 1965 (Box 66)
  - National Ballet Society, 1964 (Box 66)
  - National Catholic Theatre, 1961 (Box 66)
  - National Council on the Arts, 1956-1965 Feb., 1965 March-April, 1965 May-August, 1965 Sept.-Dec., 4 folders (Box 66)
  - National Council on the Arts, 1966 Jan.-Dec., 1967-1970 and undated, 5 folders (Box 67)
  - National Council on the Arts, undated (Box 68)
  - National Council on the Arts: Agency for the 4th Meeting (Box 68)
  - National Council on the Arts: Agenda for the Sixth Meeting, 1966 August (Box 68)
  - National Council on the Arts: Agenda for the Seventh Meeting, 1966 Dec. (Box 68)
  - National Council on the Arts: Agenda for the 10th Meeting, 1967 Nov. (Box 68)
  - National Council on the Arts: Agenda for the 13th Meeting, 1968-Nov. (Box 68)
  - National Council on the Arts: Agenda for the 14th Meeting, 1969 Jan. (Box 68)
  - National Council on the Arts: Agenda for the 15th Meeting, 1969 May (Box 69)
  - Nationial Council on the Arts: Agenda for the 16th Meeting, 1969 Oct. (Box 69)
  - National Council on the Arts: Chasm, 1966 Mar-Aug, 1966 Sept.-1969, 2 folders (Box 69)
  - National Council on the Arts: Christmas Cards, 1968 (Box 69)
  - National Council on the Arts: Hanks, Nancy, 1968-1969 (Box 69)
  - National Council on the Arts: Notebook, 1965-1966 (Box 69)
  - National Council on the Arts: Notebook, 1968, 3 folders (Box 70)
  - National Council on the Arts: Notebook, 1970 Jan.-1970 May, 2 folders (Box 70)
  - National Council on the Arts: Notebook, 1970 May (Box 71)
  - National Council on the Arts: Stevens, Roger, 1957-1966 Aug.- Sept.-1967 and undated, 2 folders (Box 71)
  - National Council on the Arts: Stevens, Roger--Letters Supporting, 1968-1969 (Box 71)
  - National Council on the Arts and Government, 1959-1967 (Box 72)
  - National Council on the Arts and Humanities 1964-1965 (Box 72)
  - National Council on the Humanities, 1965-1966 (Box 72)
  - National Endowment for the Arts, 1965-1968 Nov., Dec. 23 1969, Dec. 24-1970 and undated, 3 folders (Box 72)
  - National Endowment for the Arts: Draft Proposals, 1970-1971 (Box 72)
  - National Endowment for the Humanities, 1966-1969 (Box 73)
  - National Foundation on the Arts and Humanities, 1962-1963 Oct., Nov.- 1966, Apr.-Dec., 4 folders (Box 73)
  - National Foundation on the Arts and Humanities, 1966 Dec.-1967 March-Oct., 1967-1968 and undated, 4 folders (Box 74)
  - National Foundation on the Arts and Humanities: Grants-In-Aid--Alabama--Colorado, undated (Box 75)
  - National Foundation on the Arts and Humanities: Grants-In-Aid--Connecticut--Idaho, undated (Box 75)
  - National Foundation on the Arts and Humanities: Grants-In-Aid--Illinois--Maryland, undated (Box 75)